hardcoretube.net 2008-12-17

# HardcoreTube.net - Upload your porn and share your amateur hardcore sex movies

### HardcoreTube Privacy Notice

 **HardcoreTube** recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others who use [www.HardcoreTube.net](http://www.hardcoretube.net/) or other web sites owned or operated by HardcoreTube value their privacy. This Privacy Notice details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the HardcoreTube Sites. HardcoreTube provides this Privacy Notice to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the HardcoreTube Sites.

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the Terms of Use. Your use of the HardcoreTube Sites and any personal information you provide on the HardcoreTube Sites remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use.

Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the HardcoreTube Sites becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Notice.

> ## The Information HardcoreTube Collects

  * **User Provided Information:** You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to HardcoreTube when choosing to participate in various activities on the HardcoreTube Sites such as uploading videos, posting messages in our forums or in the video comments section, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists.   
 
  * **Cookies Information:** When you visit the HardcoreTube Sites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. HardcoreTube uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the HardcoreTube Sites may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.   
 
  * **Log File Information:** When you use the HardcoreTube Sites, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

> ## The Way HardcoreTube Uses Information

  * If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the HardcoreTube Sites, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the HardcoreTube Sites.   
 
  * Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload videos or send messages through the HardcoreTube Sites and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any videos that you submit to the HardcoreTube Sites may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.   
 
  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major HardcoreTube Site changes or for customer service purposes).   
 
  * We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the HardcoreTube Sites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends.   
 
  * We use cookies and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the HardcoreTube Sites; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. 

> ## When HardcoreTube Discloses Information

  * We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.   
 
  * We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.   
 
  * We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the HardcoreTube Sites.   
 
  * We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.   
 
  * HardcoreTube also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that HardcoreTube believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of HardcoreTube, our Users or others. 

> ## Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the HardcoreTube Sites, in which case HardcoreTube may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your [profile page](http://www.hardcoretube.net/login.php). Please note that media files uploaded by Users to the HardcoreTube Sites cannot be removed and remain subject to our Terms of Use.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.

> ## Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

HardcoreTube allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the HardcoreTube Sites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the HardcoreTube Sites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

HardcoreTube does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks HardcoreTube to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the HardcoreTube Sites, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. HardcoreTube's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

> ## Our Commitment To Childrens' Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, HardcoreTube does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the HardcoreTube Sites from persons under 18 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 18. If you are under 18 years of age, then please do not use or access the HardcoreTube Sites at any time or in any manner. If HardcoreTube learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 18 years of age has been collected on the HardcoreTube Sites without verified parental consent, then HardcoreTube will take the appropriate steps to delete this user/information.

> ## In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy

In the event that HardcoreTube is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

> ## Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "effective date" below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of the HardcoreTube Sites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.

For revisions to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personal information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information.

**Date Last Modified:**  
This Privacy Notice was last modified July 22, 2007.

**Contact Information:**  
Please contact HardcoreTube with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice by mailing to this address: [webmaster@hardcoretube.net](mailto:webmaster@hardcoretube.net).
